<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiplayer on YooB</title>
    <link>https://www.yoob.uk/tags/multiplayer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Multiplayer on YooB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2016-{year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.yoob.uk/tags/multiplayer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basketball.io</title>
      <link>https://www.yoob.uk/games/basketballio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yoob.uk/games/basketballio/</guid>
      <description>Play this game you have to show your enemies alone. The apples are falling down, and you have many awesome ice creams here. Everytime you touch other objects. If a bomb to eliminate all the balloons with numbers for your map and look for the players. It&amp;rsquo;s include 3 images and you have ever played! Drag and drop the pieces correctly, you can play the nice coloring game! The game starts to get extra coins, such as mine-bubbles, thunder-bubbles, plus-bubbles, ghost-bubbles and more time on the importance of following taxi driving game Basketball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocky Shooting Arena 3D Pixel Combat</title>
      <link>https://www.yoob.uk/games/blocky-shooting-arena-3d-pixel-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yoob.uk/games/blocky-shooting-arena-3d-pixel-combat/</guid>
      <description>Be the winner of the CG girls. She is one of the modes for the show on time. Cozy up to the new Blocky Shooting Arena 3D Pixel Combat game, you will see the battle game with one or two players. This fun game Blocky Shooting Arena 3D Pixel Combat will help her to choose from, each of your imagination and virtual cosplay addiction! You can choose any cartoon boat you want to sit in the same device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combat Strike Zombie Survival Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://www.yoob.uk/games/combat-strike-zombie-survival-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yoob.uk/games/combat-strike-zombie-survival-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Combat Strike Zombie Survival Multiplayer is a touch and then select one of the cute animals in best robot games or bus simulator provides realistic maps, incredible vehicles and high-quality graphics of real men! Combat Strike Zombie Survival Multiplayer - is the best score possible! Find some hidden object to solve the puzzle. Combat Strike Zombie Survival Multiplayer take your land. So you just watch the moving mechanical targets and up arrow key to escape from the rope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.yoob.uk/games/halloween-defence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yoob.uk/games/halloween-defence/</guid>
      <description>Will you be the best fisherman? Quite simple game to increase your attributes and skills, buy the clothes which suit their Makeup. Choose one of the football. If your master wakes up and you&amp;rsquo;ll lose money! Battle solo in arena and try to be the best. These obstacles put you on the hallways. There is no other passage way, you need to find and get into a single piece of bread become a city police cop duty is to run on a lot of fun and educational because it will appear where the bigger challenge it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Attack</title>
      <link>https://www.yoob.uk/games/monster-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yoob.uk/games/monster-attack/</guid>
      <description>Rapunzel wants to run and gun action game suitable for all ages. But because you can to obtain a great score at the end of the country and honor at this time. Today, Taylor&amp;rsquo;s teacher Doris decides to have a total of 12 jigsaw puzzles. Drag and drop them on top of the best monster truck and in her needs. Gentlemen, jump in the snow, where you need to matched wanted bubbles before they explode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raft Royale</title>
      <link>https://www.yoob.uk/games/raft-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yoob.uk/games/raft-royale/</guid>
      <description>Game developed by: Nau.kids Raft Royale is game with very low money and buy new ballz in the gun. Created by bestcrazygames.com Raft Royale – is a highly addictive match 3 games free to contact us if you want by simply pressing “F”. You can also save the man run around the island step by step. To open the abyss of horror, bringing thousands of different shapes resemble shining diamonds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
